

QIANQIAN.W
Visual Designer
(206) 953 0326
qianqiandesign@gmail.com
qianqiandesign.com

STATEMENT

I am a designer with refined taste, absolute care for detail, and deep curiosity that gives me empathy for users and their pain points. I take great pride in my ability to innovate and a creative process that results in improved user experience and performance.

EXPERIENCES

11/2019 - Now

Marketing Designer II

@ Evernote - Redwood City

- Led and developed large-scale campaigns and product launches from initiating concepts through execution, defining and expanding campaign themes across channels
- Refreshed the Evernote website serving 20MM users per month. Conceptualized and developed new design treatment that enhanced market position and improved performance
- Created instructions and guidance for designers on the usage of creative resources,
 and introduced naming conventions as well as localization process for assets
- Developed scalable style guides, email templates and website component libraries to maintain consistency across the brand company wide
- Supported brand storytelling across digital and print platforms, and worked closely with stakeholders to ensure branded content delivered on the brief, goals, and expectations

10/2019 - 11/2019

Senior UI/UX Designer

@ Leadvisor - San Jose

- Worked closely with the executive team, defining a vision for design that set the direction for product development
- Created wireframes for the internal communications, designed dynamic and interactive prototypes, and turned team's ideas into testable artifacts

03/2018 - 09/2019

Product Designer

@ Jyve - San Francisco

- Collaborated with product managers and engineers to solve design problems and create flexible and scalable UI and UX solutions for mobile apps
- Interviewed the target users, built the user flows for the core product platforms
- Developed wireframes, as well as highly functional and interactive prototypes, and created the necessary assets and graphic elements

05/2017 - 03/2018

Product Designer

@ Pillow - San Francisco

- Performed as a lead designer for marketing launch including banners, brochures, door hangers, email campaigns, presentation decks, iconography, and landing pages
- Worked with Engineer and Marketing team to design interaction and user interface for dashboard and responsive website

SKILLS

HTML Animation Figma CSS User Research Sketch Adobe Photoshop Interactive Design Sass Speed Wireframing Adobe Illustrator Javascript Adobe After Effects Concept Development jQuery Font-end Development Adobe InDesign CMS

EDUCATION

09/2016 - 05/2019

Academy of Art University

Master of Art in Web Design & New Media

09/2013 - 06/2015

University of Washington, Information School

Master of Science in Library and Information Science